Guide to the Cornell A cappella groups collection, 1985-2002.
Cornell A Cappella Groups Collection, 1985-2002.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell A Cappella Groups Collection, 1985-2002.
37-6-3236.
Alfred Grunwell.
7 cubic ft.
Cassette tapes, phonograph records, compact disks.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library.
Includes master tapes, phonograph records, and compact disks of various Cornell a cappella groups.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes master tapes, phonograph records, and compact disks of various Cornell a cappella groups, including Cayuga's Waiters, Touchtones, Class Notes, Nothing But Treble and Hangovers.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Grunwell, Alfred.; Cayuga's Waiters (Musical group).; Class Notes (Musical group).; Cornell University--Students.; Hangovers (Musical group).; Nothing But Treble (Musical group).; Touchtones (Musical group).
Subjects:
Popular music--United States--1981-1990.; Choruses, Secular (Men's voices, 4 parts), Unaccompanied.; Popular music--United States--1991-2000.; Choruses, Secular (Women's Voices), Unaccompanied.
Form and Genre Terms:
Audiotapes.; Compact disks.; Phonograph records.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIALS
Music by the groups can also be found in the Music Library Collection.
CONTAINER LIST
- Cornell A Cappella Groups
  - ADATS - Cayuga's Waiters (small tapes are DATS), 2001-2002 (Box 1)
  - Three tapes of the Hangovers, 1992, 2002 (Box 1)
  - Class Notes - Cut Class V, 2001-2002 (Box 1)
  - Touchtones - Call Waiting, 1991, 2001 (Box 1)
  - F-1 format tapes, 2001-2002 (Box 1)
  - Master Tapes of Cayuga's Waiters, 1985 (Box 2)
  - LPs of Cayuga's Waiters - 12 Degrees North, Presenting Cayuga's Waiters, Hangin Out, Laughed Out of Town, 1985-1993 (Box 2)
  - Master Tapes of Class Notes, 1990, 1993 (Box 2)
  - Master Tapes of Touchtones, 1990 (Box 2)
  - LP - Hangovers - Face Time, 1985-1993 (Box 2)
  - Datadiscs and DATS - Cayuga's Waiters (Box 3)
  - 39 copies of Class Notes CD Naturally (Box 3)
  - Mastertapes - Cayuga's Waiters, 1986-1990 (Box 4)
  - 2-inch multitrack Master tapes - 1991, 1992, 1980s-1990s (Box 5)
  - 6 Cayuga's Waiters Master tapes, 1980s (Box 5)
  - 3 2-inch Multitrack Master tapes - Cayuga's Waiters, 1992-2002 (Box 6)
  - 4 ADAT Masters, 1992-2002 (Box 6)
  - 4 Master tapes, 1980s-2002 (Box 7)
  - Digital tape, Cayuga's Waiters - Mighty Love (Box 7)
  - 7 DAT tapes - Cayuga's Waiters, 1999-2002 (Box 7)
  - 1 DAT- Pamoja - Ni mix (Box 7)
  - Nothing But Treble posters, Undated (Folder 1)